{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Protecting Mobile Devices ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1.  Of the following options, what is the best for keeping your phone secure and effective. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Leave it at home ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Leave it at home\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Secure it with a screen lock ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Secure it with a screen lock\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si20585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Leave it in the car ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20585_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Leave it in the car\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21927","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21931","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Get an RFDI-blocking case ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21927_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Get an RFDI-blocking case\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Securing your phone with a screen lock means that if someone steals your phone, they won’t be able to just access all the personal information that is stored on it. Locking can be based on a pin, password, facial recognition, or fingerprint. Make sure to take a look at your phone security settings and pick the lock that works best for you.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B  Securing your phone with a screen lock means that if someone steals your phone, they won’t be able to just access all the personal information that is stored on it. Locking can be based on a pin, password, facial recognition, or fingerprint. Make sure to take a look at your phone security settings and pick the lock that works best for you.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si20589","si21931","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.  Of the following options, what is the best for keeping your phone secure and effective.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_188","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_188","roles":{}},{"id":"si16169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_580","roles":{}},{"id":"si16077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_569","title":"2.   If your phone is stolen at work, what should you do? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_570","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_571","title":"Accuse your coworkers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"322","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Accuse your coworkers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16099","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_572","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_573","title":"Hunt down the thief ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16099_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"324","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Hunt down the thief\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22516","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22520","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Report it to the IT service desk or to the police ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22516_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Report it to the IT service desk or to the police\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22531","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22535","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Wait until it turns up ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22531_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wait until it turns up\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22546","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22550","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Flee the country ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22546_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Flee the country\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_579","roles":{}},{"id":"si16187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_80","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_81","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19375","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19389","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19705","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19718","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19733","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19746","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19761","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19774","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19789","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19802","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_576","title":"Correct - Answer: C  If you realize that your phone is missing and is not in your possession, you should report it. If it is a government issued work phone, you must report to the IT service desk (250-387-7000 or Toll Free 1-866-660-0811 option 4), otherwise you can report theft of a personal phone to the police. Do not try to track, approach or confront any suspected thieves. Doing so would put yourself in danger, leave it to trained security professionals who can proceed safely.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_577","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  C  If you realize that your phone is missing and is not in your possession, you should report it. If it is a government issued work phone, you must report to the IT service desk (250-387-7000 or Toll Free 1-866-660-0811 option 4), otherwise you can report theft of a personal phone to the police. Do not try to track, approach or confront any suspected thieves. Doing so would put yourself in danger, leave it to trained security professionals who can proceed safely.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_578","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16211","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_188","si16077","si16092","si16103","si22520","si22535","si22550","si16187","si16201","si19375","si19389","si19705","si19718","si19733","si19746","si19761","si19774","si19789","si19802","si16157"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16211"},"question":{"interactionId":"16057","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2.   If your phone is stolen at work, what should you do?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_177","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_177","roles":{}},{"id":"si16375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_594","roles":{}},{"id":"si16272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_581","title":"3.  Why are phones a frequent target for criminals? (select all that apply) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_582","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16287","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_583","title":"They have great apps ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16287","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16417q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si16283_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They have great apps\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16294","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_584","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_585","title":"They are small and easy to grab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16298","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16417q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si16294_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They are small and easy to grab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si21319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"They carry a lot of personal information ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21323","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16417q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21319_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They carry a lot of personal information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"There is gold inside phone parts ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21338","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16417q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21334_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"There is gold inside phone parts\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21981","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21985","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"They operate on wireless signals that can be insecure. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21985","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16417q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si21981_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They operate on wireless signals that can be insecure.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22561","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22565","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Criminals can’t afford their own phones ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22565","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16417q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22561_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Criminals can’t afford their own phones\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_593","roles":{}},{"id":"si16393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_82","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16407","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_83","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19417","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19817","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19858","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19873","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19886","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19901","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19914","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_590","title":"Correct -Answer: B, C, E  Mobile phones are small and often easy to steal, they carry a lot of personal information, and it is easy to accidentally transmit that personal information over insecure connections. Phones are often marketed as an easy convenience, but you need to be mindful of security around you phone. If treated carelessly, they can become a huge security risk.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16351","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_591","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B, C, E  Mobile phones are small and often easy to steal, they carry a lot of personal information, and it is easy to accidentally transmit that personal information over insecure connections. Phones are often marketed as an easy convenience, but you need to be mindful of security around you phone. If treated carelessly, they can become a huge security risk.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16363","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_592","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16417","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_177","si16272","si16287","si16298","si21323","si21338","si21985","si22565","si16393","si16407","si19403","si19417","si19817","si19830","si19845","si19858","si19873","si19886","si19901","si19914","si16363"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16417"},"question":{"interactionId":"16252","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.  Why are phones a frequent target for criminals? (select all that apply)\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B","C","E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_178","roles":{}},{"id":"si16536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_604","roles":{}},{"id":"si16455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_595","title":"4.  Many companies make promotional offers over text messages. If you receive a text with a link for a great deal, should you click on the link? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_596","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_597","title":"Yes. Click on the link ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16466_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"338","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes. Click on the link\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_598","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_599","title":"No. Don’t click on the link ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16477_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"340","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No. Don’t click on the link\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16530","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_603","roles":{}},{"id":"si16554","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_84","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16568","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_85","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19431","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19929","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19942","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19970","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19985","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19998","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20013","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20026","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_600","title":"Correct -Answer: B   As a general rule, you should not click on links in text messages. It is very difficult to verify the sender of a text, and phones make it difficult to safely check if it is a suspicious link.  That doesn’t mean all text promotions are bad, you can still get promo codes for online stores, just make sure you use them on a safe and legitimate website.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16512","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_601","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B  As a general rule, you should not click on links in text messages. It is very difficult to verify the sender of a text, and phones make it difficult to safely check if it is a suspicious link.  That doesn’t mean all text promotions are bad, you can still get promo codes for online stores, just make sure you use them on a safe and legitimate website.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16524","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_602","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16578","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_178","si16455","si16470","si16481","si16554","si16568","si19431","si19445","si19929","si19942","si19957","si19970","si19985","si19998","si20013","si20026","si16524"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16578"},"question":{"interactionId":"16435","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4.  Many companies make promotional offers over text messages. If you receive a text with a link for a great deal, should you click on the link?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_179","roles":{}},{"id":"si16697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_614","roles":{}},{"id":"si16616","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_605","title":"5. You need to use mobile data for secure messaging and transactions, but you are concerned about the security of the connection. What can you do? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_606","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16631","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_607","title":"Don’t do it ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Don’t do it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_608","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_609","title":"Use it for only a very short time before cutting off the connection ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16638_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use it for only a very short time before cutting off the connection\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21357","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Connect to a WiFi hotspot before proceeding ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Connect to a WiFi hotspot before proceeding\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21368","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Use a VPN ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21368_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use a VPN\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16691","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_613","roles":{}},{"id":"si16715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_86","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16729","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_87","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19459","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19473","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20041","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20054","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20069","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20082","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20097","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20125","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20138","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_610","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Using a VPN can wrap your communications in a layer of encryption that will keep your information secure. You should not send sensitive information through public WiFi or mobile networks without using a VPN, otherwise it is easy for people to snoop on your information.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16673","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_611","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  Using a VPN can wrap your communications in a layer of encryption that will keep your information secure. You should not send sensitive information through public WiFi or mobile networks without using a VPN, otherwise it is easy for people to snoop on your information.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16685","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_612","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16739","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_179","si16616","si16631","si16642","si21357","si21372","si16715","si16729","si19459","si19473","si20041","si20054","si20069","si20082","si20097","si20110","si20125","si20138","si16685"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16739"},"question":{"interactionId":"16596","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5. You need to use mobile data for secure messaging and transactions, but you are concerned about the security of the connection. What can you do?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_180","roles":{}},{"id":"si16858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_624","roles":{}},{"id":"si16777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_615","title":"6.  What should you do regularly with your phone? (check all that apply) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16788","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_616","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16792","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_617","title":"Perform updates ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16792","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16900q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si16788_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Perform updates\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16799","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_618","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_619","title":"Download the latest apps ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16803","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16900q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si16799_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Download the latest apps\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22056","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22060","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Physically secure your phone to your person ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22060","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16900q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22056_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Physically secure your phone to your person\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22071","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22075","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Backup your data ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22075","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16900q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22071_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Backup your data\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22086","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22090","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Jailbreak your phone ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22090","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16900q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22086_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Jailbreak your phone\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22588","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22592","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review your installed apps and delete unused apps ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22592","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16900q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22588_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Review your installed apps and delete unused apps\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_623","roles":{}},{"id":"si16876","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_88","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16890","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_89","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19487","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20153","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20166","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20181","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20194","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20209","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16846","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_622","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21378","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Answer:  A,C,D,F  Regular care is key for keeping your phone secure. You should make sure the phone and apps are kept updated, your data should be backed-up regularly. On top of that, you should occasionally review what apps you have installed and delete the unused apps, this will keep you secure in case any app becomes compromised. You should not jailbreak your phone, as that can open up many security vulnerabilities and it can allow dangerous apps.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21382","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  A,C,D,F  Regular care is key for keeping your phone secure. You should make sure the phone and apps are kept updated, your data should be backed-up regularly. On top of that, you should occasionally review what apps you have installed and delete the unused apps, this will keep you secure in case any app becomes compromised. You should not jailbreak your phone, as that can open up many security vulnerabilities and it can allow dangerous apps.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16900","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_180","si16777","si16792","si16803","si22060","si22075","si22090","si22592","si16876","si16890","si19487","si19501","si20153","si20166","si20181","si20194","si20209","si20222","si20237","si20250","si16846"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16900"},"question":{"interactionId":"16757","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  What should you do regularly with your phone? (check all that apply)\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","C","D","F"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_181","roles":{}},{"id":"si17049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_636","roles":{}},{"id":"si16957","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_625","title":"7.  When getting a new mobile device, you find that it has many new settings and features. What should you do with these settings? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_626","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_627","title":"Trust the manufacturer and leave them on the default settings ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Trust the manufacturer and leave them on the default settings\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_628","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_629","title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything off ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16979_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything off\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22603","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22607","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything on ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22603_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything on\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22618","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Take the time to learn what each setting and feature means for your device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22618_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Take the time to learn what each setting and feature means for your device\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si17043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_635","roles":{}},{"id":"si17067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_90","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_91","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19515","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19529","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20265","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20278","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20293","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20306","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20321","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20362","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17013","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_632","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  New features are added to mobile devices all the time. When you get a new device, you are likely going see many new features and different setting configurations. Not every manufacturer sets the defaults with your privacy and security in mind. Make such you understand what the main settings mean, even if you aren’t delving into advanced configuration menus.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17025","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_633","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  New features are added to mobile devices all the time. When you get a new device, you are likely going see many new features and different setting configurations. Not every manufacturer sets the defaults with your privacy and security in mind. Make such you understand what the main settings mean, even if you aren’t delving into advanced configuration menus.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17037","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_634","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17091","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_181","si16957","si16972","si16983","si22607","si22622","si17067","si17081","si19515","si19529","si20265","si20278","si20293","si20306","si20321","si20334","si20349","si20362","si17037"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17091"},"question":{"interactionId":"16937","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  When getting a new mobile device, you find that it has many new settings and features. What should you do with these settings?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_182","roles":{}},{"id":"si17225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_648","roles":{}},{"id":"si17133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_637","title":"8.  New and exciting apps are released all the time for utilities, education or games. What will help you stay secure when using mobile apps? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_638","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_639","title":"Look into the apps and the publisher ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"360","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Look into the apps and the publisher\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_640","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_641","title":"Deny permission requests from apps that don’t make sense ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17155_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"362","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Deny permission requests from apps that don’t make sense\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21580","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21584","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Delete the apps when you are done with them ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21580_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Delete the apps when you are done with them\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21595","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21599","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21595_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si17219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_647","roles":{}},{"id":"si17243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_92","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17257","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_93","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19543","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20390","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20405","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20418","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20433","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20446","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20461","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20474","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_644","title":"Correct - Answer: D  Every app on your phone is another possible target to breach your security. Make sure to review and only download apps from trusted publishers. Don’t give apps any permission that they shouldn’t have. A newsreader app should not have access to your contacts, microphone and GPS location. Finally, make sure to delete apps when you are done with them to reduce any possible vulnerability.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_645","title":"Incorrect - Answer: D  Every app on your phone is another possible target to breach your security. Make sure to review and only download apps from trusted publishers. Don’t give apps any permission that they shouldn’t have. A newsreader app should not have access to your contacts, microphone and GPS location. Finally, make sure to delete apps when you are done with them to reduce any possible vulnerability.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_646","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17267","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_182","si17133","si17148","si17159","si21584","si21599","si17243","si17257","si19543","si19557","si20377","si20390","si20405","si20418","si20433","si20446","si20461","si20474","si17213"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17267"},"question":{"interactionId":"17113","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8.  New and exciting apps are released all the time for utilities, education or games. What will help you stay secure when using mobile apps?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Marchquiz2020","class":"project","title":"Marchquiz2020","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide16211","Slide16417","Slide16578","Slide16739","Slide16900","Slide17091","Slide17267","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide16211q1","Slide16417q2","Slide16578q3","Slide16739q4","Slide16900q5","Slide17091q6","Slide17267q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide16211","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide16417","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide16578","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide16739","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide16900","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide17091","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide17267","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}